This is another thing I learned from
Michael Dell. The advice that Dell gave
me when I had dinner with him, and he
does this in story form, too, cuz that
guy's been running his business for 41
years. It's insane. His whole thing is
you're not going to be taken out by
competition. You're going to sabotage
yourself. Entrepreneurs sabotage
themselves. And the amount of people
that were doing the same thing I was
doing, they were ahead of me. They were
ahead of me, but then they got the 500
million a year in revenue and they're
like, I have a house on Lake Austin now.
They're in the same city. They're doing
the same thing as in the same city and
they're smoking them. They're ahead of
them by a few hundred million and
they're like, "Oh, I can chill now." No,
you can't. Cuz you got Michael Dell
right across the river and he's not
gonna chill.